

Aleena Mirza

≥ aleenamirza2003@gmail.com | 0310-1004301 in https://www.linkedin.com/in/aleena-mirza-052948238



@ Gulshan-e-Iqbal, Block-7, Karachi, Pakistan

Education

Hospitality Management

Jan 2022 - Present

COTHM

Employment

HR Manager Jan 2023 - Present

The Tech Turbine

HR Manager Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

Mad Bee Digital

HR Manager June 2022 - Aug 2022

Hello International Marketing Solutions Official

• A software house + call center.

Nov 2021 - June 2022 **Talent Acquist Officer**

Virtue Xolutions

Social Media Manager Jan 2020 - Nov 2021

Lifestyle Pakistan

Team Manager Jan 2021 - July 2021

Football Club Karachi

• Won a few big tournaments and participated in Nationals as well.

Personal details

Date of birth

January 11, 2003

Gender

Female

Skills

Recruitment

Strategic communication

Social Media Marketing

Team building

Problem-solving abilities

Creative

Organizational skills

Computer proficiency

Football Coach

Jan 2021 - June 2021

Ground Zero

- Led and managed age groups of 6 to 16 years.
- Number of players increased in my coaching era.

Football Coach

July 2019 - Jan 2021

Gulshan Soccer Academy

- Led a senior team as captain as well.
- Won a few tournaments like Mini Olympics.

Profile

Social Media Manager with 1.5 years of experience creating, implementing, and optimizing social media strategy for company and brand. Relentlessly focused on generating new revenue using social media. Ready to bring this energy and commitment to an environmentally focused aesthetic brand like 3D Lifestyle. Also dedicated and reliable physical educational coach with 3+ years of experience in handling all age groups in almost all outdoor games. I have a couple years of experience in teaching. I have around 2 years of experience in HR. I know how to create processes to enhance strategic business outcomes, Background includes benefits administration, full staffing/recruitment, employee relations, employee development, and compensation. Excellent Interpersonal, problem-solving skills, Successful track record of contributions which increased organizational effectiveness. I am good in handling the HR department well, always loyal to the employer and a responsible person when it comes to work, which I am passionate about.

Extracurricular activities

- Currently managing my own Women Football and Basketball teams called 'Team Off Limit' in Karachi.
- National player of Football.
- Co-Founder of an NGO called 'Smile Pakistan'.
- Working in Music videos and Modelling for local brands.
- Creating contents on social media to spread awareness on various topics.
- National Gold Medalist in roller skating.

Languages

Urdu

English

Hobbies

- Reading
- Travelling
- Exploring
- Sports
- Writing
- Movies
- Teaching